<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<parrot_language>
    <phrases>
        <phrase>Isn't that right, Sprinkles?</phrase>
        <phrase>Sprinkles knows.</phrase>
        <phrase>Can you here us Sprinkles?</phrase>
        <phrase>haha</phrase>
        <phrase>Ah funny you should mention that. Pat Morton was just talking to me about this on Friday.</phrase>
        <phrase>Aye! Ye be right!</phrase>
        <phrase>Always. It's job security.</phrase>
        <phrase>Oh yeah, we did sit near each other for a bit.</phrase>
        <phrase>That was a terrible time on that project. There were some major barriers to _not_ breaking builds.</phrase>
        <phrase>Get to walking</phrase>
        <phrase>Awwww</phrase>
        <phrase>Thank you for t hat</phrase>
        <phrase>…How does my underpowered laptop manage to run the coding challenge 33% faster than my monster desktop at home? What witchcraft is this, Jimmy Dotson?</phrase>
        <phrase>I just google "Panera Pantera" and it's a thing ... "Vulgar Display of Flour"</phrase>
        <phrase>Laptop is on a desk too...</phrase>
        <phrase>Jonathan Thompson has joined the channel</phrase>
        <phrase>WOOO!</phrase>
        <phrase>How are captains selected for each ship?</phrase>
        <phrase>I do sense a *mutiny* brewing...</phrase>
        <phrase>Its a direct message command nina</phrase>
        <phrase>If anyone is still having issues with the DM commands let me know :slightly_smiling_face:</phrase>
        <phrase>Michael Morris, Haven't forgotten about that one. Just haven't had time just yet. Be on the look out in the near future for it though</phrase>
        <phrase>I am a totally honest broker!</phrase>
        <phrase>Okay, I'll trust you with all mine.</phrase>
        <phrase>Generally, though EXIF isn't a very tight standard so nothing is stopping you from storing an address or something super generic like "USA".</phrase>
        <phrase>In my dress!</phrase>
        <phrase>Who says she's having fun?</phrase>
        <phrase>"sinking" nice!</phrase>
        <phrase>:sob:so close</phrase>
        <phrase>Will you make better Mac 'n Cheese if there's a point bonus?</phrase>
        <phrase>granted it won't be many extra points.</phrase>
        <phrase>A bowl of cheap mac n' cheese with a bottle of rum shoved into it?</phrase>
        <phrase>The cheese is just rum. . .</phrase>
        <phrase>Taped over KFC container with "Richard's Mac and Cheese" scribbled on the outside</phrase>
        <phrase>Dave and it's got mashed potatoes.</phrase>
        <phrase>Go high class... Church's.</phrase>
        <phrase>oh yeah man. Knock it out</phrase>
        <phrase>get to steppin' Colton\</phrase>
        <phrase>not yet. Something like !stormOnTheHorizon?</phrase>
        <phrase>Call it !ridersOnTheStorm</phrase>
        <phrase>or !battenDownHatches</phrase>
        <phrase>hes good thanks :thumbsup:</phrase>
        <phrase>:slightly_smiling_face:</phrase>
        <phrase>obfusicatino</phrase>
        <phrase>Hey, I played Vampire, I got this.</phrase>
        <phrase>Who said it doesn't</phrase>
        <phrase>That's frightening</phrase>
        <phrase>Say hello to "Mack -The Blue Fox - Pepper" you scurvy sea dogs!!  Soon to be captain of the "Blue Insanity"!!  Argggghhh!</phrase>
        <phrase>Or potential code challenge theme???</phrase>
        <phrase>I'm efficient.</phrase>
        <phrase>Isn't that where Haymon keeps his cheap guitars?</phrase>
        <phrase>I have cheap guitars?</phrase>
        <phrase>duh</phrase>
        <phrase>Bye Bethany</phrase>
        <phrase>Josh Mayfield is building his army up</phrase>
        <phrase>He's at SSI for the week. I think that counts as walking the plank.</phrase>
        <phrase>to write a program to decrypt messages in a bottle.</phrase>
        <phrase>That means there's a lot of secrets... Hmmm...</phrase>
        <phrase>is LOGO training exactly what it sounds like?</phrase>
        <phrase>You haven't been to many coding challenge demos, have you? :thinking_face:</phrase>
        <phrase>I mean. You have to go outside in the rain.</phrase>
        <phrase>awe shoot lol it is a cute command though!</phrase>
        <phrase>Sprinkles is never wrong, sir.</phrase>
        <phrase>i haven't forgot about this one :slightly_smiling_face:</phrase>
        <phrase>doh</phrase>
        <phrase>haha</phrase>
        <phrase>shoot</phrase>
        <phrase>hahahahaha</phrase>
        <phrase>lol too meticulous</phrase>
        <phrase>Is that who's been unlucky enough to have to walk the most, or who's called for walks the most?</phrase>
        <phrase>Lol had me scared for a second. Thought something was wrong with Sprinkles</phrase>
        <phrase>Put him in the long boat till he's sober?</phrase>
        <phrase>NEVAH!</phrase>
        <phrase>YOU CAN'T MAKE ME!</phrase>
        <phrase>ACCESS DENIED!</phrase>
        <phrase>Caleb is exempt from earning all points</phrase>
        <phrase>That escalated quicky :pacman: :pcsghost:</phrase>
        <phrase>wait I thought he was sliding downhill</phrase>
        <phrase>I can see both if I try, like any number of illusions.</phrase>
        <phrase>I now see both, and I hate it</phrase>
        <phrase>I don't think he's got a way to make Sprinkles do thread things.</phrase>
        <phrase>I think you need a better random number generator</phrase>
        <phrase>Look at that old event on that list!</phrase>
        <phrase>I think I just need more hacker quotes</phrase>
        <phrase>Put him in the bilge and make him drink it.</phrase>
        <phrase>Tie him to the taffrail when she's yardarm under.</phrase>
        <phrase>Sprinkles is currently out of office. He'll reply to your message upon his return.</phrase>
    </phrases>
</parrot_language>