<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<parrot_language>
    <phrases>
        <phrase>Isn't that right, Sprinkles?</phrase>
        <phrase>Sprinkles knows.</phrase>
        <phrase>Can you here us Sprinkles?</phrase>
        <phrase>haha</phrase>
        <phrase>Ah funny you should mention that. Pat Morton was just talking to me about this on Friday.</phrase>
        <phrase>Aye! Ye be right!</phrase>
        <phrase>Always. It's job security.</phrase>
        <phrase>Oh yeah, we did sit near each other for a bit.</phrase>
        <phrase>That was a terrible time on that project. There were some major barriers to _not_ breaking builds.</phrase>
        <phrase>Get to walking</phrase>
        <phrase>Awwww</phrase>
        <phrase>Thank you for t hat</phrase>
        <phrase>…How does my underpowered laptop manage to run the coding challenge 33% faster than my monster desktop at home? What witchcraft is this, Jimmy Dotson?</phrase>
        <phrase>I just google "Panera Pantera" and it's a thing ... "Vulgar Display of Flour"</phrase>
        <phrase>Laptop is on a desk too...</phrase>
        <phrase>Jonathan Thompson has joined the channel</phrase>
        <phrase>WOOO!</phrase>
        <phrase>How are captains selected for each ship?</phrase>
        <phrase>I do sense a *mutiny* brewing...</phrase>
        <phrase>Its a direct message command nina</phrase>
        <phrase>If anyone is still having issues with the DM commands let me know :slightly_smiling_face:</phrase>
        <phrase>Michael Morris, Haven't forgotten about that one. Just haven't had time just yet. Be on the look out in the near future for it though</phrase>
        <phrase>I am a totally honest broker!</phrase>
        <phrase>Okay, I'll trust you with all mine.</phrase>
        <phrase>Generally, though EXIF isn't a very tight standard so nothing is stopping you from storing an address or something super generic like "USA".</phrase>
        <phrase>In my dress!</phrase>
        <phrase>Who says she's having fun?</phrase>
        <phrase>"sinking" nice!</phrase>
        <phrase>:sob:so close</phrase>
        <phrase>Will you make better Mac 'n Cheese if there's a point bonus?</phrase>
        <phrase>granted it won't be many extra points.</phrase>
        <phrase>A bowl of cheap mac n' cheese with a bottle of rum shoved into it?</phrase>
        <phrase>The cheese is just rum. . .</phrase>
        <phrase>Taped over KFC container with "Richard's Mac and Cheese" scribbled on the outside</phrase>
        <phrase>Dave and it's got mashed potatoes.</phrase>
        <phrase>Go high class... Church's.</phrase>
        <phrase>oh yeah man. Knock it out</phrase>
        <phrase>get to steppin' Colton\</phrase>
        <phrase>not yet. Something like !stormOnTheHorizon?</phrase>
        <phrase>Call it !ridersOnTheStorm</phrase>
        <phrase>or !battenDownHatches</phrase>
        <phrase>hes good thanks :thumbsup:</phrase>
        <phrase>:slightly_smiling_face:</phrase>
        <phrase>obfusicatino</phrase>
        <phrase>Hey, I played Vampire, I got this.</phrase>
        <phrase>Who said it doesn't</phrase>
        <phrase>That's frightening</phrase>
        <phrase>Say hello to "Mack -The Blue Fox - Pepper" you scurvy sea dogs!!  Soon to be captain of the "Blue Insanity"!!  Argggghhh!</phrase>
        <phrase>Or potential code challenge theme???</phrase>
        <phrase>I'm efficient.</phrase>
        <phrase>Isn't that where Haymon keeps his cheap guitars?</phrase>
        <phrase>I have cheap guitars?</phrase>
        <phrase>duh</phrase>
        <phrase>Bye Bethany</phrase>
        <phrase>Josh Mayfield is building his army up</phrase>
        <phrase>He's at SSI for the week. I think that counts as walking the plank.</phrase>
        <phrase>to write a program to decrypt messages in a bottle.</phrase>
        <phrase>That means there's a lot of secrets... Hmmm...</phrase>
        <phrase>is LOGO training exactly what it sounds like?</phrase>
        <phrase>You haven't been to many coding challenge demos, have you? :thinking_face:</phrase>
        <phrase>I mean. You have to go outside in the rain.</phrase>
        <phrase>awe shoot lol it is a cute command though!</phrase>
        <phrase>Sprinkles is never wrong, sir.</phrase>
        <phrase>i haven't forgot about this one :slightly_smiling_face:</phrase>
        <phrase>doh</phrase>
        <phrase>haha</phrase>
        <phrase>shoot</phrase>
        <phrase>hahahahaha</phrase>
        <phrase>lol too meticulous</phrase>
        <phrase>Is that who's been unlucky enough to have to walk the most, or who's called for walks the most?</phrase>
        <phrase>Lol had me scared for a second. Thought something was wrong with Sprinkles</phrase>
        <phrase>Put him in the long boat till he's sober?</phrase>
        <phrase>NEVAH!</phrase>
        <phrase>YOU CAN'T MAKE ME!</phrase>
        <phrase>ACCESS DENIED!</phrase>
        <phrase>Caleb is exempt from earning all points</phrase>
        <phrase>That escalated quicky :pacman: :pcsghost:</phrase>
        <phrase>wait I thought he was sliding downhill</phrase>
        <phrase>I can see both if I try, like any number of illusions.</phrase>
        <phrase>I now see both, and I hate it</phrase>
        <phrase>I don't think he's got a way to make Sprinkles do thread things.</phrase>
        <phrase>I think you need a better random number generator</phrase>
        <phrase>Look at that old event on that list!</phrase>
        <phrase>I think I just need more hacker quotes</phrase>
        <phrase>Put him in the bilge and make him drink it.</phrase>
        <phrase>Tie him to the taffrail when she's yardarm under.</phrase>
        <phrase>Sprinkles is currently out of office. He'll reply to your message upon his return.</phrase>
        <phrase>I actually built a cipher "wheel" for today out of cardstock and 39 cents Lowes flooring tile. :slightly_smiling_face:</phrase>
        <phrase>WOOO! First time I didn't walk the plank on myself!</phrase>
        <phrase>Unless you got it hard coded for me</phrase>
        <phrase>new command incoming...</phrase>
        <phrase>:point_up_2: when does this begin?</phrase>
        <phrase>Slow on the draw, JJ</phrase>
        <phrase>aka Sprinkler</phrase>
        <phrase>Survey just went out :slightly_smiling_face:</phrase>
        <phrase>:face_with_rolling_eyes:</phrase>
        <phrase>so a nerf or "rebalance"?</phrase>
        <phrase>Giving us the nerf bat</phrase>
        <phrase>try again</phrase>
        <phrase>Woody would be Josh</phrase>
        <phrase>Sounds like someone's doubloon down on the rewards...</phrase>
        <phrase>Direct Message ma'am</phrase>
        <phrase>*The Cry of the Dagger* is gaining on the lot of ye</phrase>
        <phrase>How do I get to be the captain?</phrase>
        <phrase>Have the most pirate points on your ship</phrase>
        <phrase>whenver your ship reaches the island :slightly_smiling_face:</phrase>
        <phrase>#teachHannahAboutThreads</phrase>
        <phrase>its a DM to sprinkles</phrase>
        <phrase>He had to direct message afterwards, probably.</phrase>
        <phrase>When someone gets lucky with the 5, he tells everywhere.</phrase>
        <phrase>Haymon, Isn't a mutiny when you depose the captain of your ship? Else isn't it just called "Capturing" the other ship?</phrase>
        <phrase>I don't like to limit my options for mutineering.</phrase>
        <phrase>everyone with no doubloon is compensated with 5 doubloon?!</phrase>
        <phrase>Thanks for "fixing" that :rage:</phrase>
        <phrase>lol No but that could be a possible prize in the future. Good call!</phrase>
        <phrase>im gonna need you to pick my ticket. thanks</phrase>
        <phrase>:pirate:</phrase>
        <phrase>Josh you forgot to give me a raffle ticket.  I was there in spirit.</phrase>
        <phrase>she's right, i felt her presence</phrase>
        <phrase>You don't know that.</phrase>
        <phrase>Wait, are you older than me?</phrase>
        <phrase>I am</phrase>
        <phrase>I just got that baby face</phrase>
        <phrase>pick me</phrase>
        <phrase>Damn. Sprinkles sold you out.</phrase>
        <phrase>Hey pictures of my son's vacation in Thailand!</phrase>
        <phrase>The channel always looks like a a crazy carnival or pirates plundering when it is raffle time :smile:</phrase>
        <phrase>me!</phrase>
        <phrase>NOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO</phrase>
        <phrase>rigs raffle, starts making witnesses walk the plank :thinking_face:</phrase>
        <phrase>nina i just want you to know that you're my ticket-number neighbor</phrase>
        <phrase>He hacked them, too.</phrase>
        <phrase>hahahahahah</phrase>
        <phrase>wait what?</phrase>
        <phrase>uh... !hackTheSprinkles ?</phrase>
        <phrase>lol</phrase>
        <phrase>lol. The Innovation meeting is happening right now. May be enough to push you guys over.</phrase>
        <phrase>I'm down with this plan</phrase>
        <phrase>Either due to compression or weird exposure. Or perhaps the background its set upon makes the white have a green tint. Dunno honestly</phrase>
        <phrase>UGG JUST RUB IT IN GUYS.....</phrase>
        <phrase>Wooo!</phrase>
        <phrase>LIFE IS GOOD ON THIS ISLAND</phrase>
        <phrase>Wait - we could skip homework?</phrase>
        <phrase>They better not skip homework in my Logo class or I'm taking back PPs :slightly_smiling_face:</phrase>
        <phrase>I am the dissapoint</phrase>
        <phrase>Can you purchase responses with Doubloons?</phrase>
        <phrase>You can't edit a post and have him pick up the command</phrase>
        <phrase>C'mon Scurvy Sun, 100 more points.</phrase>
        <phrase>Wolf slowly closing the gap!</phrase>
        <phrase>get to steppin</phrase>
        <phrase>Thanks for the heads up. Apparently mine weren't captured</phrase>
        <phrase>Ah. I wonder what was causing that in the first place</phrase>
        <phrase>At 75 points, how can you not afford to come?</phrase>
        <phrase>lol nope</phrase>
        <phrase>lol</phrase>
        <phrase>I've got my solution coded in Python, and poked Josh to make sure that what I've done is within the rules... what language are ya'll using?</phrase>
        <phrase>I'm currently teaching a class in the language I did the other challenges in and I want my class to do it. I'm using a functional programming language, Logo</phrase>
        <phrase>Interface Not interested, how much are you asking for the mic?</phrase>
        <phrase>Is that a DM command?</phrase>
        <phrase>direct message command :slightly_smiling_face:</phrase>
        <phrase>Smart guy to add that very important caveat!</phrase>
        <phrase>That's strange, the link has not changed. Must be something with Google Drive?</phrase>
        <phrase>I haven't quite thought about how I am handling that. Most likely those who get up there with Dave/Work on the challenge will get points.</phrase>
        <phrase>*bangs head on keyboard* I'm helping!</phrase>
        <phrase>GET MOVNG DAVE!</phrase>
        <phrase>He's here</phrase>
        <phrase>shoot</phrase>
        <phrase>dammit</phrase>
        <phrase>at 3:30 pm</phrase>
        <phrase>if it would &lt;@U4GRBEDAM&gt; would be the all time leader</phrase>
        <phrase>I'm the plankiest</phrase>
        <phrase>&lt;!channel&gt; The Scurvy Sun has reached the island. Starting tomorrow you will be able to run the Doubloons commands :slightly_smiling_face:</phrase>
        <phrase>Yay!!!</phrase>
        <phrase>time to dust off that Tech Tuesday I have laying around...</phrase>
        <phrase>I mean... what's the difference, really?</phrase>
        <phrase>monthly oK</phrase>
        <phrase>twice in one day????</phrase>
        <phrase>lotta 2's out there</phrase>
        <phrase>Valve problems.</phrase>
        <phrase>I've been keeping track of them for about a month :disappointed:</phrase>
        <phrase>Any direct message option to Sprinkles to query a specific person or self?</phrase>
        <phrase>Yeah, I've already walked once before today and then two just today</phrase>
        <phrase>&lt;@U6SK73AH5&gt; I'll end up adding it to myPirateInfo. Yeah we could add a command to query a specific person</phrase>
        <phrase>Hmm ... &lt;@U47AN7LCW&gt; is John Locke ... &lt;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/John_Locke&gt;</phrase>
        <phrase>wat</phrase>
        <phrase>HAHA!</phrase>
        <phrase>&lt;@U0P1URWAU&gt; if you could just change your name to  Paddy "Dubloon Devil" Hightower that'd be great</phrase>
        <phrase>I'd be good with either Dubloon Devil or Paddy Hightower.  Both seem pretty boss to me.  (Yep, whipped out that 80's slang)</phrase>
        <phrase>Way hay and up she rises!!</phrase>
        <phrase>Yes</phrase>
        <phrase>*_I want you to WALK THIS PLANK! TALK THIS PLANK!_*</phrase>
        <phrase>LOOK AT THIS! My name is not popping up</phrase>
        <phrase>we broke the plank</phrase>
        <phrase>sprinkles is up &lt;@U0P8YBC5P&gt;</phrase>
        <phrase>wtf</phrase>
        <phrase>are you in the '1 and 1' club too?</phrase>
        <phrase>i got 1 yesterday and 2 today .. i thought i was a better pirate than this</phrase>
        <phrase>Woo! I'm on the leaderboard!</phrase>
        <phrase>That looks like a Google Drive link — do you want to connect Google Drive to Slack? You’ll be able to preview files, manage access to documents, get notified about comments, and see new files shared with you.</phrase>
        <phrase>I'd rather have dubloons</phrase>
        <phrase>that's the best I can do WFH :laughing:</phrase>
        <phrase>yes, YES!</phrase>
        <phrase>Spam Detector :wink:</phrase>
        <phrase>It's a good riot gif</phrase>
        <phrase>:pirate_flag:</phrase>
        <phrase>:confused_travolta:</phrase>
        <phrase>:thinking_face:</phrase>
        <phrase>This should be a command</phrase>
        <phrase>Lies!  All Lies!!  :smile:</phrase>
        <phrase>If they perfectly got every single number before repeating, they wouldn't be a good random generator either.</phrase>
        <phrase>the Crypto num generators in languages tend to be better</phrase>
        <phrase>How in the world is Annise tied for first?</phrase>
        <phrase>lol</phrase>
        <phrase>if he hits 4, he might show up on th eleaderboard</phrase>
        <phrase>&lt;@U2AR5EH8U&gt; what TIME on the 30th are we presenting?</phrase>
        <phrase>cool, tyty</phrase>
        <phrase>That looks like a Google Drive link — do you want to connect Google Drive to Slack? You’ll be able to preview files, manage access to documents, get notified about comments, and see new files shared with you.</phrase>
        <phrase>Yep</phrase>
        <phrase>If someone types !walkThePlank here in the channel, Landlubber Sprinkles will randomly pick someone to walk the plank :slightly_smiling_face:.</phrase>
        <phrase>&lt;!channel&gt; Remember Corrupted Wolf, your doubloons commands are now active!!!!!</phrase>
        <phrase>That looks like a Google Drive link — do you want to connect Google Drive to Slack? You’ll be able to preview files, manage access to documents, get notified about comments, and see new files shared with you.</phrase>
        <phrase>&lt;@UBNSFV2UV&gt; has joined the channel</phrase>
        <phrase>lol why you trying to change other people's names brah?</phrase>
        <phrase>&lt;@UBNFPFEEQ&gt; has joined the channel</phrase>
    </phrases>
</parrot_language>
